Introducing this just in English pod news and feature show featuring Jordan the
intern who refused to do coffee to make coffee he used to do it but he makes it
hello welcome back to another edition of this just in as Marco mentioned we are
joined with Jordan the intern intern for what Italian pod no Jordan like a last
name like Michael Jordan is Jordan Jordan can be both it can be both I'll admit
that most people I meet remember my name by it's like Michael Jordan but no it's
it's Michael Jordan without the Michael Jordan the intern who refused to make
coffee I'm telling you these days are spoiled spoiled now it's just that you
know it's you Marco asking me and I'm back back when I was an intern when I
I used to take copies I did every kind of different coffee make coffee go for the
laundry what about shining well you know when I was an intern I chose no so it so
Jordan what is it that you do exactly well I do nothing besides nothing and
refusing to do work for Marco I work with the dialogues for English pod I
quality check for a French pot in Italian pot and you know I take orders
from people besides Marco okay so what is it with Marco Marco you have no
authority here none nobody respect me in this office I'm telling you why it's
because it's a bunch of no respect for mark is like an English skill coming
through on that last month shut the front door glad to have you with us Jordan
glad to be here mark shut the front door and well hopefully you and Marco can
solve your differences among hierarchies here in the office yeah we in a call
doing a coffee maybe we can meet for a coffee maybe you can show him how to
make it no maybe Jordan doesn't make coffee cuz he doesn't know how I asked
him to make tea if he didn't know how he told me if you give me the teabag and
the cup maybe I can think about it you know that's the thing
Jordan hey my coffee I make is very user of the week user of the week who's
the user of the Jordan do you know I have no idea you don't know who's the
mark knows I know our user of the week is from Japan this week oh nice you know
where Japan is I know where Japan is I'm actually a big Japan fan myself okay who
is no no we'll leave that for the last so why don't we take a look at the lessons
that we have coming up next week Jordan do you know what the lessons are for next
week are you're just looking at a piece of paper I think that's Spanish pod
lesson okay this is what I do here people say go in this booth to record
your voice and I go yes sir and then mark it tells me you go wait I got Catherine
is your boss are you calling her sir well when you tell me your court stuff or yes
man she can be quite intimidating or if Marco tells me to do work I say shut the
front door well we have on Monday we have part seven of I'm sorry I love you
part seven what's happening now well right now we're trying to go back to a
romantic aspect of the series because we had some explosions we had some news and
so now we're going back to more romantic stuff so was she pregnant well no no she
wasn't pretty well haven't you listened to all the others yeah of course and six
parts go on well Jordan doesn't know I'm sure does Jordan know do you know
Jordan do I know what does Jordan know I know I know that I am an unpaid
intern yeah yeah like this leg good here's a critique for practice like yeah
good all right to make friends with your employees yeah of course romance it's
always you know it's a great thing to learn you know because you know if you
need to say some you know I love you and you know you have a girlfriend not the
current time I do not have a girlfriend to all the girl listeners out there
right now I don't have to be so low I don't have the accent I don't have you
know this sexy accent so I just have that you know I just got my rough you
know Philadelphia accent next lesson all right next lesson we're getting a haircut
who's gonna get a haircut I Jordan needs one no Marco needs one you just got one
yeah look you always look the same Leo of course you always have the same you want
me to 20 years no I mean the hair always the same style yeah let's go for
something new why don't you get some highlights or so they don't even get
yeah we don't even grow a Jerry curl that's what Jerry girl what a Jerry
curl what's that it's like you got like the curls back it's real greasy it's
gonna look good on you it'll look good you know like MacGyver that's more like
70s like Conan the barbarian no no that would also get on you a nice smile it
would be great all right so on Wednesday we'll be learning how to tell the
hairstylist what type of haircut very important especially if you're a girl very
important well not only a girl cuz if you're a guy you can't speak the
language you go in and all of a sudden you know yeah but come on if they do
like if they cut my hair in a different way I go like ah that's not really what
I wanted whatever yeah but if it happens like if it happens to a girl most of the
girls oh yeah and all the people around there will be in trouble you haven't
noticed you don't have a sister no that's why well she's young she doesn't
cut her hair yet all right and on Friday part 5 of new guy in town all right so
we're gonna have a series here another series some suspense and we're gonna be
learning some great vocabulary of asking for help different ways and
explaining how do you explain what problem you have or what you need maybe
that's what you need your part if you explain what you need to Jordan you
might have your coffee in your desk or your desk every morning yeah you're
lacking communication skills break down a communication or you know you don't know
let me tell you about the breakdown I'll tell you about you know that English
powder had a coffee pot that every morning would dispense happiness in form
of a cup of coffee cups to all the employees of practice language yeah one
day I arrived to the office this coffee pot is broken who broke it next to the
coffee pot stands who if not our friend Jordan the intern an evil smile and he
says Marco good morning would you like some coffee as broken the coffee pot I
have I have no information about this coffee pot and next lesson I want more
for just information about anything you're in you know I am the underpaid
under educated part of the internship here you're as useless as the Olympic
dolls of Brigitte you're like baby no automatic air hands dryer in a bedroom I
don't know what that they're useless have you ever gone to a bathroom try to
dry your hands on those automatic air blowers great amazing it never dries up
you're probably off pressure you're supposed to shake excess water from
your hands first yeah there you go then I could do it by myself I'm with
Leon this all right user of the week user of the week finally
all right our user of the week is Michi Shige
Konnichiwa, Michi Shige
Hopefully you did not butcher her name
Gageki desu ka
Nice, you picked up some Japanese
Wana ni arigato seunara
Sayonara
Okonomiyaki
so what about her why shut up Leo
why is she user of the week
why stop saying
he's taking over
he's gonna leave him
why is she user of the week
which is she spicy
no she's sweet
she must be spicy
in a good way
you were there with your family
by the way
just sound
bye
you're spicy
all right well she was posting some really good comments on the website following our lessons
and you know what else on her profile
she's got the lyrics of
hand in my pocket by Alanis Morissette
which she says
Jordan the internet will sing for us
maybe not
come on
come on Jordan
I just couldn't do it justice
we'll give you a little bit here
and another one
but Jordan
you know that's the thing I'd butcher it
and you know we'd lose you know consumers
because you know their ears would start bleeding when I sang
how old are you?
I am 18
really? I thought you were like 20
he's 18 outside
I thought you were like 18 and a half
yeah man
no I turned 19 on May 19th
which is coming up soon
and you're gonna turn 19 without having sung
Alanis Morissette
tell you what maybe on my birthday
maybe on my birthday I'll come in
because I'm working on my birthday
they're spoiled
they think they own their place
you know
I'm not that I just you know don't want to make coffee
it's a moral thing
sing for us
it's a political stand
do something
entertain us
thank you
we just did a double jump period
double back flip
alright guys that's all the time for today
we will see you guys next week
please come to our website englishpod.com
and don't forget to visit us on Facebook
we'll have also like a little button
at the top of the page
it's a link to donate
for Jordan the internet survivor
because it's not paid
you can donate
he never takes showers
he's always wearing the same clothes
actually a deodorant
it will be great
I mean Jordan what's your name
thanks
alright guys we'll see you guys next time
bye
EnglishPod.com